1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Track Order/track your order"))
13. setText(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/txtField_Email"), "agung.priyadi@gtech.digital")
17. setText(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/txtField_Verification Code"), "")
21. click(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/btn_Send"))
25. verifyTextPresent("The verification code has been sent, please check in the mailbox.", false)
29. setText(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/txtField_Verification Code"), "999999")
33. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/btn_Continue"), 10)
37. click(findTestObject("Guest User/Track Your Order/btn_Continue"))
41. verifyTextPresent("Verification code error.", false)
45. takeScreenshot()
49. closeBrowser()